This ends now!
Time resume your flow!
What?
And who might you be?
How long have you been lurking?
Answer me! Who are you?
And your neck!
Explain that mark you have immediately!
What is this sensation?
What's going on?
How did you manage to make
the arrow slip from my grasp?
I said halt!
I'm not done with you yet!
Reveal your face!
This second...
Why am I on my knees?
This man, he appeared atop the same
wall where Silver Chariot melted.
Could this be the arrow's doing?
Hey, Mista!
Something weird's going up!
This feeling...
Is this what...
the others...
what's going?
The fate of the fate of my fate.
The fate of my fate.
The game's door.
Let's go.
The end of the day, the
future, and the future?
The life of the life, and
the desire to stay gold!
I don't know, I don't know? No, no,
no...
It remains only the result
that you will be destroyed.
The eternal life exists only in me.
You can sing songs of sadness
in the world without time.
Let's go!
When I die, when I die, I will die.
Hello, the beginning of the day.
Oh, damn.
Can't believe I fell asleep.
Huh?
Geez, what happened?
Oh crap, sun's up already?
Yeah, we were out cold for a while.
Though I can't remember exactly how. Huh?
Huh?
What the hell?
My hands are all soaked in blood!
Shit!
But... but how?
Something get us while we were down?
Are you hurt anywhere else?
Giorno!
Don't just stand there, idiot!
Get your ass behind some cover now!
If you're injured, start patching up!
Wait, how can you even
tell if Giorno's hurt?
Do you see him? Where'd he go?
Hey, Giorno!
Hurry up and hide!
Damn it!
Where did he run off to?
Man, this sucks!
I can't see jack shit from way over here!
Hey, come on, Trish.
You look around, too.
You see him anywhere?
You just said he was hurt, didn't you?
Did you hit your head?
I mean... Huh?
My dude.
Do you even hear yourself?
No!
The hell are these?
Dude, what's going on?
How'd I grow a pair of chesticles?
Holy crap, my tingling is gone!
Where'd you go, little guy?
I'm serious, this is an emergency!
Hey, Giorno!
Why are your hands bleeding?
What happened to them?
You freaking moron!
It's you, damn it!
I'm talking to you!
Wait, but I'm not!
I mean, the blood scared me shitless, too.
But weirdly enough, I don't feel a thing.
It must be from all that freaky mold
Giorno said he was gonna fix it,
but I guess he must have
missed a couple of cuts.
Hey,
it's possible the blood
stripping down from my
shoulder We talking about
the same mold cuz I thought
What happened do you know?
Did I really sleep through
it all I feel really weird
What the hell?
Dude, this isn't my face.
I switched bodies with
Giorno. No, wait. Our minds.
Our minds switched.
Could this have happened
while we were sleeping?
To me and Giorno?
Mista and Trish?
What kind of messed up
voodoo crap is this?
Last I checked, people's minds
couldn't just trade bodies?
Oh.
Oh, my God. Am I? Did we?
What horrible curse is this?
I look hideous.
Damn.
My armpits stink.
Dear Lord, just kill me now.
Oh, come on now, Trish, that's just rude.
We got bigger things to worry
about than the smell of my pits,
like the stand that attacked us.
This doesn't look like the
handiwork of Emperor Crimson,
which can only mean we've got another
bad guy out there trying to mess with us.
Damn it!
Was it another one of his weird
lackeys that did this to us?
I don't think so.
The boss had already made it all
the way to the Coliseum himself.
There's no sense in him passing
the baton to an underling.
Plus, Mista and Narancia
keep talking about an attack.
But is this really all there is to it?
Our souls may have swapped bodies,
but none of us are actually hurt.
So then...
Hey, Giorno!
Whatever ends up happening, just
don't forget I'm technically older.
You gotta be kidding me with this, right?
Do everything to clean under your damn
nails and shave your knuckles too!
It's called basic hygiene! Look it up!
Every part of me stinks!
Couldn't I have switched
with someone who showers?
Why'd it have to be Mista?
Well, I don't know.
Maybe it's because we happen to
pass out right next to each other.
That aside, you know words can hurt
just as much as bullets sometimes.
It can't be that bad. Hey! Whoa there!
What exactly do you think
you're doing with those fingers?
It's not what you think at all!
I wasn't trying to cop
a feel, I swear to God!
It's just the elastic fit, you know?
You'd better kick those
hands out of my panties!
Alright, sorry!
If I catch you touching anything
else, I'll bury you alive.
Fine, jeez, I get it.
I'm just saying these panties
feel like a bunch of rubber
bands racing to see who can
split my ass in half first.
And your bra's a real hugger, too.
Listen, Dick,
you even think about getting anywhere
near my skirt again, I'll kill you.
Do you hear me?
There will be nothing left of you!
Narancia!
That's not Narancia, you idiot.
You pay no attention,
but I'm the dope, right?
Cut that out!
Hey, guys, I was wondering, if all of
us swap minds, did Bucciarati swap too?
So far, it's me and Giorno
and Mista and Trish.
If my first guess was correct and
we swapped with the closest guy,
then where's Bucciarati now?
I've been watching him this whole time.
The man hasn't so much as twitched.
I'm worried about him. Is he okay?
Wait, Narancia!
Don't approach him! Huh?
I'm sure it happened to him, too.
Whoever's in there might not be friendly.
So we should tread carefully.
That's what you're saying, am I right?
It depends on what happened
before we got here.
Is there a way to even tell?
We need to know who was closest to him,
and what happened to the boss
and the man waiting for us.
Narancia!
Scan the area with Lil' Bomber!
That's what I've been trying
to do, but something's wrong.
It's not working.
My my stand is refusing to show.
Come on, little bomber!
Damn it.
Why the hell won't you come out? Shit!
If our stands don't work.
Narancia, wait!
Just give it some time. Huh?
Ah!
Little bomber!
Ah! Nice! He's fast!
I didn't even see him fly past me!
Could he always do that?
I have no idea what's going
on, but it feels hella good!
Does anyone else be lit, or is it just me?
Nah, man, I feel the same rush as you!
Happy to report my
bullets are still with me.
In fact, they're hitting
harder than ever before!
I just ripped through six
whole metal railings with
a single shot and my focus
has never been sharper.
Yeah, that's great and all but what kind
of stand swaps the souls of its victims?
Whoever did this to us they're up to
something as much as I hate to think about it.
It could be an enemy
I don't see anyone else.
It looks like we're all alone guys.
I can't tell where the boss is
I just see lots of randos.
And it looks like they're all out cold.
There's too many of them
and they're all spread out.
My radar can't count them all.
No, wait, hold on.
I think I see someone moving.
There's a cop coming too.
My god, what a dream?
What the hell is this?
That police chick was smoking hot.
Especially when I cupped her?
Tweet, tweet, tweet, tweet, tweet.
Man, I think all these people
had their souls swapped too.
Yeah, that's what it looks like.
It's starting to stir up some chaos.
Shit, solving this is gonna
be a bitch and a half, huh?
Hey, Giorno, what are you doing?
I'm using the ground as a medium to
search for lingering soul energy.
So far, nothing. Damn it.
Who could Bucciarati have
swapped with? Narancia.
Or Giorno, rather.
If you're worried about the possibility
that Bucciarati switched with the boss,
I think I can give you
a little peace of mind.
That's not the case.
I can't sense a trace of
the boss's soul on him.
If that's what really happened,
then I would know for sure.
Still,
this is gonna sound strange,
but I can't sense his presence
anywhere for that matter.
It's like he just disappeared.
That worries me.
I guess until Bucciarati
wakes up, we just won't know.
We should keep a close eye on him.
It hurts.
Without a doubt, Diavolo is your foe.
You hear?
Man, this hurts.
I beg you to listen.
Arantia, no.
You are Giorno Giovanna, aren't you?
Golden Wind!
Hold on.
I'm not puppeteering this
turtle in any way. No tricks.
The one you are speaking
to is the turtle itself.
My name is Jean-Pierre Polnareff.
I am the one who asked you to
come meet me here at the Coliseum.
But in my fight with Diavolo, I was
forced to abandon my body for this turtle.
You're kidding me.
The hell's a Polnareff?
Please, spare me a moment to explain.
I acted this way only because
Diavolo afforded me no other choice.
Right now,
the event that you are experiencing
as you stand there gawking
was brought about by the very
arrow I had hoped to give you.
I still hope to convey
the secret of its power,
even as I desperately fight
to hang on to my soul.
Wait!
You're saying all of this
happened because of the arrow?
To put it in specific terms,
It was my Stan Silver Chariot that
triggered this when he took hold of it.
My original body lies lifeless upstairs,
but by the grace of the
arrow my soul survived
when it latched on to this turtle's form.
There's a body over here.
He's telling the truth.
Whatever did him in made a gigantic mess.
Is that really all you see?
Nothing else?
Hey, if everything you're
saying is really true,
doesn't that mean your
Silver Chariot or whatever
it's called can put us back
in our original bodies?
No.
In my current state,
I cannot control Chariot, nor do
I have any means to withdraw him.
And I cannot discern his location either.
As of now, he is like an agitated
cannon that's been set loose.
So your stance just wandering
around wreaking havoc?
How could you let that happen?
Stop!
Please just tell us what
happened to the boss.
How did he find you?
More importantly, how do we find him?
I don't know.
One moment I saw him standing right
before me, and then he was gone.
Listen, you must focus.
The arrow is not your foe,
but nor is it your friend.
What I'm about to explain to you
is the essence of hope itself.
Let's begin with an incident seemingly
trivial to most from around two years ago.
Having somehow survived
my encounter with Diavolo,
I clawed my way to safety and
found refuge in a small village.
It was there and then that
the incident took place.
The arrow I'd retrieved in Egypt had gotten
itself stuck behind a chest of drawers.
a mild displeasure but
annoying nonetheless an
able-bodied person could
have resolved the problem
without much difficulty
but for someone like me
the task proved a little
challenging I briefly
considered leaving it be
before the idea of using
chariot struck me that's
when it happened with
nary a warning the arrow
sliced chariots finger
it happened so fast as
you know the arrow brings
out stands in humans.
But should a stand happen to be
the pierced party, the full extent
of the arrow's history is unknown to me.
But I'm beginning to
understand what was in
the mind of its creator.
We've yet to witness the
full power of a stand.
Much more lies
hidden than one could imagine.
Suddenly, birds were falling from the sky.
Insects hid behind the leaves as
cattle collapsed to the ground.
Lastly, the farmers fell
into a deep slumber as well.
And while I myself felt far from normal,
the effects on me were eclipsed
by what Chariot had endured.
Taken by a foreboding feeling, I seized
the arrow from him before he lost himself.
Then, as if nothing had happened,
everything went back to normal.
Not long after, a most ominous
realization dawned on me.
Whoever possessed enough
power to control the arrow
could in turn steer the
minds of all living things.
That said, it cannot be me.
I've grown much too weak.
So I've been lying in wait for
brave warriors like yourselves,
willing to take the fight
straight to Diavolo.
Unfortunately for me, that
Kana has me outclassed.
So all this mind control stuff
that you're talking about,
is it the same thing that's happening now?
Like we didn't actually
switch souls after all?
No.
As I said earlier, it's the arrow's doing.
But as I cannot control it, the extent
of its power isn't something I can grasp.
Even so, its potential is undeniable.
You must retrieve the arrow!
Stop Chariot before the boss
does, and take it back from him!
To defeat Emperor Crimson,
you'll have no other choice but to
harness this weapon's full potential!
If we're gonna recapture the arrow,
we'll have to destroy Silver Chariot.
Am I correct to assume that?
It doesn't matter.
Once you've taken the arrow from him,
he'll inevitably finish his count of days.
Not unlike how, in
essence, I already have.
But before you all set off,
I have one last piece of
shocking information to give you.
Would you be the mademoiselle named Trish?
I'm a little hairier than usual, but...
I had a feeling...
The boss is two men.
Some hours ago, one of them took on
your appearance and deceived Bucciarati.
Tarot.
Diavolo and this lad.
They make a formidable
duo to be reckoned with.
What do you mean?
He was me?
That can't be.
The boss confides in nobody.
That's why no one knows his true face.
I'm really not sure I get it myself, but
I know I saw him, that strange young man.
Had it not been for him, Diavolo would
have never gotten as close to me as he did.
You're kidding.
How can he be two people?
I mean...
Giorno, something's moving.
From nine o 'clock, Uno Signale.
I see him.
It's a person.
They're heading for the
Colosseum's eastern entrance.
No way!
I know that face!
That's gotta be him! It's Diablo!
Narancia, it's showtime.
Get Lil' Bomber. Jonah, wait!
To the left!
Look closely at the figure in the dark!
He was there all along!
The arrow has completely transformed him!
He's now Chariot Requiem!
Son of a...
Crap, not good.
Diabolo's gonna beat us to him.
At this rate, he'll take the arrow.
Not so fast, kid.
Stay your hand for now.
Wait, that can't be a stand.
Is that Zipperman?
Then that means we found him.
Ain't no doubt.
It's Fucerati.
They were accusing.
Not always with a knowing.
What is just fiction?
Or what is the truth?
They have a mission.
They are the passion.
But they dare to tell us.
What's bad and what's good?
Stand up!
Join us!
Come on!
Just lead us a lie.
We are the power.
We'll be the future!
Cause we are the fighters.
Just fighting for a ride.
Thank you.